खुदा जाने ~ Khuda Jaane ~ Bachna Ae Haseeno [2008]
I bow down for prayer...
सजदे में यूँ ही झुकता हूँ...
I stop when I see you...
तुमपे ही आ के रुकता हूँ...
Does this happen to everyone?
क्या ये सबको होता है?
Why do we care about everyone?
हमको क्या लेना है सबसे?
You are my only concern now...
तुमसे ही सब बातें अब से...
You've become a blessing to me!
बन गए हो तुम मेरी दुआ !
I bow down for prayer...
सजदे में यूँ ही झुकता हूँ...
I stop when I see you...
तुमपे ही आ के रुकता हूँ...
Does this happen to everyone?
क्या ये सबको होता है?
Why do we care about everyone?
हमको क्या लेना है सबसे?
You are my only concern now...
तुमसे ही सब बातें अब से...
You've become a blessing to me!
बन गए हो तुम मेरी दुआ !
God knows that I'm smitten...
खुदा जाने के मैं फ़िदा हूँ...
God knows that I'm lost!
खुदा जाने मैं मिट गया !
God knows why this happened...
खुदा जाने ये क्यूँ हुआ है...
That how you became my God!
के बन गए हो तुम मेरे खुदा !
[♪]
If you tell I'll walk on your footprints...
तू कहे तो तेरे ही कदम के मैं निशानों पे...
and stop at your will
चलूँ रुकूँ इशारे पे
If you tell, I'll use dreams as excuse
तू कहे तो ख्वाबों का बना के मैं बहाना सा
and meet you yonder
मिला करूँ सिरहाने पे
You've taught me the matters of heart
तुम से दिल की बातें सीखी
l learnt about these ways from you
तुम से ही ये राहें सीखी
l live by dying for you!
तुमपे मर के मैं तो जी गया !
God knows that I'm smitten...
खुदा जाने के मैं फ़िदा हूँ...
God knows that I'm lost!
खुदा जाने मैं मिट गया !
God knows why this happened...
खुदा जाने ये क्यूँ हुआ है...
That how you became my God!
के बन गए हो तुम मेरे खुदा !
[♪]
My heart tells me to hide you in me...
दिल कहे के आज तो छुपा लो तुम पनाहों में...
I fear I might lose you
के डर है तुमको खो दूंगा
My heart says to watch myself, not cast an eye on this happiness...
दिल कहे संभल ज़रा ख़ुशी को ना नज़र लगा...
I fear that I might cry!
के डर है मैं तो रो दूंगा !
I make a hundred promises to you
करती हूँ सौ वादे तुमसे
Bind your heart with mine
बांधे दिल के धागे तुमसे
what has happened to you?
ये तुम्हें न जाने क्या हुआ ?
God knows that I'm smitten...
खुदा जाने के मैं फ़िदा हूँ...
God knows that I'm lost!
खुदा जाने मैं मिट गया !
God knows why this happened...
खुदा जाने ये क्यूँ हुआ है...
That how you became my God!
के बन गए हो तुम मेरे खुदा !
I bow down for prayer...
सजदे में यूँ ही झुकता हूँ...
I stop when I see you...
तुमपे ही आ के रुकता हूँ...
Does this happen to everyone?
क्या ये सबको होता है?
Why do we care about everyone?
हमको क्या लेना है सबसे?
You are my only concern now...
तुमसे ही सब बातें अब से...
You've become a blessing to me!
बन गए हो तुम मेरी दुआ !
God knows that I'm smitten...
खुदा जाने के मैं फ़िदा हूँ...
God knows that I'm lost!
खुदा जाने मैं मिट गया !
God knows why this happened...
खुदा जाने ये क्यूँ हुआ है...
That how you became my God!
के बन गए हो तुम मेरे खुदा !
[ That how you became my God ]
[ के बन गए हो तुम मेरे खुदा ]